Finding Aid for Charles Symon Papers, 1933-1983
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Charles Symon papers 1933-1983
Symon, Charles
1 linear ft.
85440 Aa 2
Historian of the C.C.C. in Michigan. Research materials.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Charles Symon (donor no. 7047 ) and came to the library in 1984.
The collection is open to research.
Historian and author of We Can Do It: A History of the Civilian Conservation Corps in Michigan, 1933-1942 (1983).
The Symon collection consists of research material created and accumulated for his book on the C.C.C. in Michigan. Included are correspondence with, and reminiscences of, former CCC members, miscellaneous CCC publications, newspaper clippings, and photographs.
Subjects:
Civilian Conservation Corps (U.S.); Conservation of natural resources--Michigan.; Depressions--1929--Michigan.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Camp Eldorado (Mich.); Camps.; Civilian Conservation Corps (U.S.); Machine shops.; Upper Peninsula (Mich.)
Contributors:
Smith, Clyde.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Research Material
  - Correspondence
    - 1980-1983, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Michigan State Archives, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
    - Post publication, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Camp Locations in Michigan (Box 1)
  - Educational Activities
    - Ludington, 1941 and 1949 (Box 1)
    - Michigan, Miscellaneous (Box 1)
  - Reunion, 1983 (Box 1)
  - CCC Publications
    - Northlander (newsletter) 1935-1936, photocopies (Box 1)
    - Annuals, 1937
      - Camp Custer District (Box 1)
      - Fort Brady District, photocopy (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Bulletins and Manuals (Box 1)
  - Manuscripts
    - Lathrop, Orrin, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Minier, Leonard, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 1)
  - Photographs (Box 1)
  - National C.C.C. publications (Box 1)